Guide to the Frederick Herzog Papers, 1947-2011 and undated (bulk 1947-1995) RL.00536
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings and Speeches Series, 1948-1999 and undated (bulk 1950-1995), 9 Boxes
  - 1950s Sermons, 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Manuscripts Subseries, 1950-1997 and undated
    Contains drafts and edits of Herzog's publications, including drafts of a collection of articles for an unfinished book on political theology. Also contains notebooks filled with research annotations and writings.
    - The Gospel of Man, undated, 4 annotated manuscripts (Box 80)
    - Manuscripts from the 1950s in Wisconsin (involvement in the labor struggle at the Kohler plant), undated (Box 81)
    - Manuscripts, 1964-1990 and undated (Box 81)
    - Methodism, Missions and Money, 1997 (Box 81)
    - Political Theology: a collection of articles for an unfinished book, undated (Box 81)
    - Sound teaching, Fall 1982 (Box 81)
    - Systematische Theologie zwischen Kapitalismus und Marxismus, undated (Box 81)
    - Translation drafts for Liberation Theology, undated (Box 81)
    - Untitled [research notes], undated (Box 81)